<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-04T00:51:38.007Z</id>
    <title>philippnagel.com/feeds</title>
    <updated>2021-06-04T00:51:38.007Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masking norms and Wokeism]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81216</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/OPOoAk50Gdw/masking-norms-and-wokeism.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the close of my latest Bloomberg column: On a related note: Have you noticed that private universities often have a stronger “woke” culture, and less free speech, than public universities? This fact is also somewhat of an embarrassment for many libertarians. Though libertarian-leaning, I am myself happy to be teaching at a public […]
The post Masking norms and Wokeism appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Anderson of TED interviews me]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81214</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/PjCQhEdSTPo/chris-anderson-of-ted-interviews-me.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 50 years of little growth, new breakthroughs in science and medicine could mean the start of a whole new era of innovation! Economist @tylercowen paints a new picture of the future — and a road map to get us there. Listen on @applepodcasts: https://t.co/jNccIENQBo pic.twitter.com/Q8nQuEWRsX — TED Talks (@TEDTalks) June 3, 2021 Here is […]
The post Chris Anderson of TED interviews me appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81207</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/5O8Lrz7yHKc/thursday-assorted-links-309.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. A visual of debt to gdp ratios.  Note the information is not strictly comparable across countries.  And where chess pieces go to die. 2. Profile of James Daunt (FT). 3. Research jobs at Charter Cities Institute. 4. United to buy 15 Boom supersonic aircraft. 5. These birds can see through magic tricks (NYT).
The post Thursday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update on Rapid Tests for COVID]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81199</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/14NhCAeH1y8/update-on-rapid-testing-for-covid.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year ago, I wrote Frequent, Fast, and Cheap is Better than Sensitive, arguing for rapid antigen tests: A number of firms have developed cheap, paper-strip tests for coronavirus that report results at-home in about 15 minutes but they have yet to be approved for use by the FDA because the FDA appears to […]
The post Update on Rapid Tests for COVID appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh fact of the day]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81213</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/qr1scf17K9M/bangladesh-fact-of-the-day-3.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T05:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, Bangladesh’s Cabinet Secretary told reporters that GDP per capita had grown by 9% over the past year, rising to $2,227. Pakistan’s per capita income, meanwhile, is $1,543. In 1971, Pakistan was 70% richer than Bangladesh; today, Bangladesh is 45% richer than Pakistan. One Pakistani economist glumly pointed out that “it is in the realm of […]
The post Bangladesh fact of the day appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you call this a new service sector job?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81208</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/QgdexV3esIo/can-you-call-this-a-new-service-sector-job.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T04:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Taube has won a computer, a whitewater rafting trip, and several grills. There’s also the kayak, the powder-blue Coors Light onesie, and the Bruce Springsteen tickets. He recently took home $10,000 from Cost Plus World Market in its “World of Joy” sweepstakes. Recently, he found himself in the running for a trip to Antarctica, which would […]
The post Can you call this a new service sector job? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Conversation with the very very smart David Deutsch]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81209</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/Y1ja4Qx9-K8/my-conversation-with-the-very-very-smart-david-deutsch.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T17:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think this episode came off as “weird and testy,” as I described it to one friend, but I like weird and testy!  Here is the audio, video, and transcript.  Here is one excerpt: COWEN: How do you think the many-worlds interpretation of quantum mechanics relates to the view that, just in terms of space, the […]
The post My Conversation with the very very smart David Deutsch appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81194</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/6u4TodTrJ_U/wednesday-assorted-links-299.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Todd Kashdan criticizing his own work. 2. “The American Economic Journal: Microeconomics (one of the very top journals that isn’t part of the holy Top-5, hallowed be thy names) managed to go an entire year without accepting a paper!”  (out of 415 submissions). 3. How the NIH behaves during an emergency. 4. Increase of […]
The post Wednesday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Vaccine Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81202</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/TfssfNT_S-U/two-vaccine-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T11:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, in an article on new vaccine boosters in USA today there is this revealing statement: Any revised Moderna vaccine would include a lower dose than the original, Moore said. The company went with a high dose in its initial vaccine to guarantee effectiveness, but she said the company is confident the dose can come down, […]
The post Two Vaccine Updates appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do individuals make more rational decisions when the stakes are higher?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81200</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/ySmloxtAYGU/do-individuals-make-more-rational-decisions-when-the-stakes-are-higher.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T05:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often yes, but this is a shibboleth of economics that doesn’t always fit the facts, as has been illustrated starkly by our behaviors during the pandemic.  Many people have taken too much risk, or been too risk-averse, even with high stakes on the line.  Here is one excerpt from my recent Bloomberg column: You might […]
The post Do individuals make more rational decisions when the stakes are higher? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olaf Stapledon movie coming!?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81206</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/xZWvz02opaU/olaf-stapledon-movie-coming.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T03:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Iceland?  Narrated by Tilda Swinton? Via Jeet Heer, and Ilya Novak.  Is it any good?
The post Olaf Stapledon movie coming!? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The age of reason is fifth grade?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81193</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/7790pmrvgug/the-age-of-reason-is-fifth-grade.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T18:12:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, the proportion of equilibrium play increases significantly until fifth grade and stabilizes afterward, suggesting that the contribution of age to equilibrium play vanishes early in life. Here is more from Isabelle Brocas and Juan D. Carrillo, forthcoming in the JPE.
The post The age of reason is fifth grade? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81184</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/ihwgsm0inyg/tuesday-assorted-links-316.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T15:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. The resilience of the U.S. corporate bond market.  And who needs a flying car? 2. Famous economists’ grave sites. 3. “Measured intelligence did not predict increased mate appeal in either study, whereas perceived intelligence and funniness did.”  Speculative. 4. Blockchain-based smart contract for Kenyan crop insurance (speculative). 5. David Beckworth podcast with Mark Carney, […]
The post Tuesday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More on Individualism and Benevolence]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81189</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/O833pPQv29Y/more-on-individualism-and-benevolence.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T11:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This paper investigates the role of individualism in charitable giving. Individualistic societies are those that value individual fulfillment, personal responsibility, and relationships with those outside one’s in-group. Though critics suggest individualism undermines virtues such as generosity, we consider contrary mechanisms first developed in the tradition of classical political economy, especially the “doux commerce” hypothesis (Hirschman […]
The post More on Individualism and Benevolence appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Largest Industries, 1890]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81191</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/j0dXrUqI53g/u-s-largest-industries-1890.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T07:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Transportation 2. Agriculture and Related Industries 3. Food, Beverages, and Tobacco Products 4. Metal, Metal Products, and Machinery 5. Textiles, Textile Products, and Clothing 6. Mining and Quarrying 7. Banking 8. Wood, Lumber, and Their Products 9. Leather and Allied Products 10. Slaughtering and Meat Packing That is from the new and excellent An […]
The post U.S. Largest Industries, 1890 appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Eris of the Month 2021: Eris Ἐρις by Matthias Jiury]]></title>
        <id>http://historiadiscordia.com/?p=9672</id>
        <link href="http://historiadiscordia.com/may-eris-of-the-month-2021-eris-%e1%bc%90%cf%81%ce%b9%cf%82-by-matthias-jiury/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T02:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Found on flickr. Send us your Eris of the Month Club submissions (more info here) by using the form at the bottom of The MGT. page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>themgt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booby Trapping the Ethereum Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>60a80b1a2c41740001d6fc2f</id>
        <link href="https://samczsun.com/booby-trapping-the-ethereum-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how an attacker could have hid a ticking time bomb on the Ethereum blockchain that, when triggered, would hard fork the entire network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samczsun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>