<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-23T00:10:48.215Z</id>
    <title>philippnagel.com/feeds</title>
    <updated>2021-06-23T00:10:48.215Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racial segregation is increasing in many parts of America]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81343</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/f3pPlax3Aac/racial-segregation-is-increasing-in-many-parts-of-america.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T18:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the nation’s largest metropolitan regions have become increasingly segregated in the last 30 years, underscoring racial inequalities that have led to poorer life outcomes in Black and brown neighborhoods, according to a study released Monday by the University of California Berkeley’s Othering & Belonging Institute. The study found that 81% of regions with more than […]
The post Racial segregation is increasing in many parts of America appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81341</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/dmAZ-F9UizU/tuesday-assorted-links-320.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Updated data on unicorns, including Chinese numbers. 2. Those new Indian service sector jobs: A CCTV Company Is Paying Remote Workers in India to Yell at Armed Robbers.  And Stalin’s Economic Council. 3. NYT profile of Emily Oster. 4. What is ranked-choice voting, and why is NYC using it? 5. More arguments about Tether […]
The post Tuesday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Fact of the Day]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81326</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/FVyCL72PL2I/new-york-fact-of-the-day-3.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T11:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYTimes: New York City built only 163,000 units of housing in the 2010s, fewer than the 205,000 created in the 1930s, during and after the Great Depression, according to a city report. From 2009 to 2018, the New York metro region added 0.5 units of housing for every new job, down from 2.2 units per […]
The post New York Fact of the Day appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milton Friedman was once a Keynesian]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81331</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/fkI2NhpLWJs/milton-friedman-was-once-a-keynesian.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T06:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early 1940s, Friedman’s own analysis of monetary policy adhered closely to the dismissive tone prevalent in much other Keynesian literature of that vintage.  His solo-authored contribution to 1943’s Taxing to Prevent Inflation, written while he was at the Treasury, plotted growth rates of the nominal money stock and nominal income for the United […]
The post Milton Friedman was once a Keynesian appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USA fact of the day]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81329</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/74tZHCBDyMw/usa-fact-of-the-day-3.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T04:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The average U.S. customer loses power for 214 minutes per year. That compares to 70 in the United Kingdom, 53 in France, 29 in the Netherlands, 6 in Japan, and 2 minutes per year in Singapore. These outage durations tell only part of the story. In Japan, the average customer loses power once every 20 […]
The post USA fact of the day appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What should I ask Zeynep Tufekci?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81342</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/rI__2bi1W_0/what-should-i-ask-zeynep-tufekci.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T19:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will be doing a Conversation with her.  So what should I ask?
The post What should I ask Zeynep Tufekci? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What crypto people get wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81340</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/r2e7ORJ9M9M/what-crypto-people-get-wrong.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T17:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That is the topic of my latest Bloomberg column, here is one excerpt: If anything, crypto is more likely to hurt the currencies of countries that are doing very poorly, such as Venezuela. Fiat currency won’t just go away, so over the long run crypto could actually boost the value of the dollar by stifling the […]
The post What crypto people get wrong appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81337</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/dm1-waiem94/monday-assorted-links-310.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Cacti poaching. 2. Chinese feminimization vs. Chinese manosphere. 3. Hard to find cross-state evidence that shelter-in-place policies worked.  And lockdowns can take more lives than they save in low-income countries. 4. Deterioration of speed. 5. Culture Ministry says all music used by government services will feature Quebec artists. 6. Swedish government falls over rent […]
The post Monday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More on Alternative Dosing]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81328</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/VZ_frAtCCNc/more-on-fractional-dosing.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T11:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some quick comments in response to questions and discussion about my paper Could Vaccine Dose Stretching Reduce COVID-19 Deaths? (written with the all-star cast of Witold Więcek, Amrita Ahuja, Michael Kremer, Alexandre Simoes Gomes, Christopher M. Snyder and Brandon Joel Tan. 1) Any method of increasing vaccine supply will require other changes in the supply […]
The post More on Alternative Dosing appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CDC is broken, our regulatory state has been failing us]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81338</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/t-GtWXH9W1M/the-cdc-is-broken-our-regulatory-state-has-been-failing-us.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T04:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was surprised by how good this NYT piece was, for instance here is one of the better diagnoses of the problem, or at least part of it: Allen disputes the notion that she and her colleagues are doing work that the C.D.C. itself should be doing; in fact, she says, the task force and […]
The post The CDC is broken, our regulatory state has been failing us appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81325</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/2guud-7fnBQ/sunday-assorted-links-319.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T20:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Is this new drinking straw an instant cure for hiccups? 2. Mark Lutter page of major instances of social change led by movements. 3. Interview with Jim Keller. 4. Which countries have appeared the most in NYT headlines over the decades? 5. Crypto joint accounts to cement relationships? 6. Tokyo Olympic eugenics?
The post Sunday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ho-hum]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81334</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/_oABIOA-BoQ/ho-hum-2.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T18:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After nearly two decades of hardcore drug addiction — after overdoses and rehabs and relapses, homelessness and dead friends and ruined lives — Gerod Buckhalter had one choice left, and he knew it. He could go on the same way and die young in someone’s home or a parking lot, another casualty in a drug […]
The post Ho-hum appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The looks gap in earnings]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81332</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/B9M8Pd4q_Tk/the-looks-gap-in-earnings.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T15:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…the magnitude of the earnings disparities along the perceived attractiveness continuum, net of controls, rivals and/or exceeds in magnitude the black-white race gap and, among African-Americans, the black-white race gap and the gender gap in earnings. Here is the full paper.  Here is an earlier MR post on lookism, and here.  Two points are worth […]
The post The looks gap in earnings appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best mask-wearing study so far?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81330</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/bVkJHGDNcv0/the-best-mask-wearing-study-so-far.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T06:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mask-wearing has been a controversial measure to control the COVID-19 pandemic. While masks are known to substantially reduce disease transmission in healthcare settings (Howard et al 2021), studies in community settings report inconsistent results (Brainard et al 2020). Investigating the inconsistency within epidemiological studies, we find that a commonly used proxy, government mask mandates, does […]
The post The best mask-wearing study so far? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-term gene–culture coevolution and the human evolutionary transition]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81322</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/rd9dDpI2JOM/long-term-gene-culture-coevolution-and-the-human-evolutionary-transition.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T04:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been suggested that the human species may be undergoing an evolutionary transition in individuality (ETI). But there is disagreement about how to apply the ETI framework to our species, and whether culture is implicated as either cause or consequence. Long-term gene–culture coevolution (GCC) is also poorly understood. Some have argued that culture steers […]
The post Long-term gene–culture coevolution and the human evolutionary transition appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Origins of the Thornley/Oswald Manuscript]]></title>
        <id>http://historiadiscordia.com/?p=9680</id>
        <link href="http://historiadiscordia.com/the-origins-of-the-thornley-oswald-manuscript/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T03:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his monograph Notes of a Neon Gringo, Kerry Thornley wrote: “When Robert Anton Wilson printed up letterheads for the Bavarian Illuminati, they carried the notice: ‘Safeguard this letter; it may be an important historical document.’ That was very much how I felt about my first little notebook, penned in 1975. I had just begun […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gorightly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Eris of the Month 2021: Eris Ἐρις by Matthias Jiury]]></title>
        <id>http://historiadiscordia.com/?p=9672</id>
        <link href="http://historiadiscordia.com/may-eris-of-the-month-2021-eris-%e1%bc%90%cf%81%ce%b9%cf%82-by-matthias-jiury/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T02:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Found on flickr. Send us your Eris of the Month Club submissions (more info here) by using the form at the bottom of The MGT. page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>themgt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booby Trapping the Ethereum Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>60a80b1a2c41740001d6fc2f</id>
        <link href="https://samczsun.com/booby-trapping-the-ethereum-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how an attacker could have hid a ticking time bomb on the Ethereum blockchain that, when triggered, would hard fork the entire network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samczsun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>