<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-14T00:11:04.689Z</id>
    <title>philippnagel.com/feeds</title>
    <updated>2021-06-14T00:11:04.689Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Iconoclastic culture that is Dutch?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81280</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/eIPs_Fws3XQ/the-iconoclastic-culture-that-is-dutch.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T18:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the delightful characteristics of the Dutch is their frankness, and this comes through in the tales—which are far from bland. As the exhibition texts explain, “the debate about the bare bottom in this Degas pastel dominated the art pages of the [Dutch] newspapers for weeks”. The question being asked was “whether in this […]
The post The Iconoclastic culture that is Dutch? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81241</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/Nt0IUgAVmEc/sunday-assorted-links-318.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T15:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Was the unicorn a now-extinct Siberian rhino? 2. What does the concept of sustainability mean? 3. Long post about Miles Davis. 4. Interview with Amartya Sen. 5. The changing nature of capital flows. 6. Houston man against Burger King upselling nudges.
The post Sunday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why was pre-Covid unemployment so low?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81228</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/3S4ntP1QoGI/why-was-pre-covid-unemployment-so-low.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T06:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a recent paper by Andreas Hornstein and Marianna Kudlyak, noting that when the authors write “current” they are (were) referring to pre-Covid times: Current unemployment, as of 2019Q4, is so low not because of unusually high job finding rates out of unemployment, but because of unusually low entry rates into unemployment. The unusually […]
The post Why was pre-Covid unemployment so low? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergent Ventures winners, 15th cohort]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81198</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/wVFskzxs-DQ/emergent-ventures-winners-15th-cohort.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T04:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emily Oster, Brown University, in support of her COVID-19 School Response Dashboard and the related “Data Hub” proposal, to ease and improve school reopenings, project here. Kathleen Harward, to write and market a series of children’s books based on classical liberal values. William Zhang, a high school junior on Long Island, NY, for general career […]
The post Emergent Ventures winners, 15th cohort appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The behavioral economics of pandemic sex]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81269</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/FjC5jHh-GsA/the-behavioral-economics-of-sex-during-the-pandemic.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T19:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another girl did ask if she could call me Fauci during sex. She said it with a straight face. I pretended that I didn’t hear and kept going, because how do you even address that? I’m not going to say yes, because that’s going to be weird. And if I say no, that kills the […]
The post The behavioral economics of pandemic sex appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81238</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/tXUBkwMoZTY/saturday-assorted-links-313.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Why did WWI take so long to start? 2. More than one layer of signaling in this story. 3. Whether various European countries have exceeded their 2006 gdp per capita highs. 4. It seems robots make us healthier. 5. Should people in academia write more on Wikipedia? 6. Even most Democrats do not favor […]
The post Saturday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[*Ages of American Capitalism*]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81258</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/SJGxtqIRVRI/ages-of-american-capitalism.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T04:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author is Jonathan Levy (U. Chicago) and the subtitle is A History of the United States, noting it is mostly an economic history from a left-mercantilist, nation-building point of view.  So far on p.95 I quite like the book, here is one excerpt: Ironically enough, in some respects Jefferson’s Empire of Liberty came to […]
The post *Ages of American Capitalism* appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I’ve been reading]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81212</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/Su53AY7QSfw/what-ive-been-reading-194.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T04:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. William Wordsworth, The Prelude, 1805 edition.  Many people who read “the Great Books” never touch this one, because it is a poem, and a long one at that (about 200 pp. in my Oxford edition).  Nonetheless a) it is one of the best poems, and b) the experience of reading it is more like […]
The post What I’ve been reading appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81271</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/0owOpkBdBdA/friday-assorted-links-314.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T17:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Not sure I have been abused for any prediction more than this one, and yet it seems true: “Democratic primary voters have been turning away this year from the anti-elite furies that continue to roil Republican politics, repeatedly choosing more moderate candidates promising steady leadership over disrupters from the party’s left wing.”  Here is […]
The post Friday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nach dem Gleichgewicht auflösen]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81275</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/0sXqv9jFaDk/nach-dem-gleichgewicht-auflosen.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T16:17:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swiss-based multinationals such as commodities trader Glencore will receive subsidies and other incentives under plans Switzerland is drawing up to maintain its competitive tax rates, even as the country prepares to sign-up to the G7’s new plan for a global minimum tax on big businesses. Bern is consulting its cantonal governments — which set their […]
The post Nach dem Gleichgewicht auflösen appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Half Dose of Moderna is More Effective Than a Full Dose of AstraZeneca]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81272</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/JM0EbL0N1p0/a-half-dose-of-moderna-is-more-effective-than-a-full-dose-of-astrazeneca.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T11:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are releasing a new paper on dose-stretching, co-authored by Witold Wiecek, Amrita Ahuja, Michael Kremer, Alexandre Simoes Gomes, Christopher M. Snyder, Brandon Joel Tan and myself. The paper makes three big points. First, Khoury et al (2021) just published a paper in Nature which shows that “Neutralizing antibody levels are highly predictive of […]
The post A Half Dose of Moderna is More Effective Than a Full Dose of AstraZeneca appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin Vernon on El Salvadoran bitcoin acceptance, from my email]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81276</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/Pl36exPvemQ/austin-vernon-on-el-salvadoran-bitcoin-acceptance-from-my-email.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T04:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sent this to [redacted, a man of substance] yesterday. LN = Lightning Network, Bitcoins layer 2 scaling solution based on channels: As far as I understand it, everyone using LN in El Salvador has primarily been using Strike. Classic crypto conundrum in that they had to centralize to get it to work. There is a […]
The post Austin Vernon on El Salvadoran bitcoin acceptance, from my email appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not that there’s anything wrong with that…]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81240</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/rwCw80AT1q8/not-that-theres-anything-wrong-with-that.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…democratic rule and high state capacity combined produce higher levels of income inequality over time. This relationship operates through the positive effect of high-capacity democratic context on foreign direct investment and financial development. By making use of a novel measure of state capacity based on cumulative census administration, we find empirical support for these claims […]
The post Not that there’s anything wrong with that… appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81261</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/teUnPg_DVY4/thursday-assorted-links-310.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T15:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Is this possible?: “Criminals may have stolen as much as half of the unemployment benefits the U.S. has been pumping out over the past year, some experts say.” 2. When should ngdp be unstable? 3. Is Nero underrated? (New Yorker) 4. Sixty times the speed of sound? (USS Princeton radar team and pilot source, […]
The post Thursday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The coming regulation of bank crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81270</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/03nO-iQ14Bg/the-coming-regulation-of-bank-crypto.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A $100 exposure in bitcoin would result in a minimum capital requirement of $100, Basel said. The standards would apply to assets created for decentralised finance (DeFi) and non-fungible tokens (NFTs), but potential central bank digital currencies were outside the scope of the consultation, it added. Here is more from the FT.  While that is […]
The post The coming regulation of bank crypto appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Eris of the Month 2021: Eris Ἐρις by Matthias Jiury]]></title>
        <id>http://historiadiscordia.com/?p=9672</id>
        <link href="http://historiadiscordia.com/may-eris-of-the-month-2021-eris-%e1%bc%90%cf%81%ce%b9%cf%82-by-matthias-jiury/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T02:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Found on flickr. Send us your Eris of the Month Club submissions (more info here) by using the form at the bottom of The MGT. page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>themgt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booby Trapping the Ethereum Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>60a80b1a2c41740001d6fc2f</id>
        <link href="https://samczsun.com/booby-trapping-the-ethereum-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how an attacker could have hid a ticking time bomb on the Ethereum blockchain that, when triggered, would hard fork the entire network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samczsun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>