<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2021-06-06T00:27:14.022Z</id>
    <title>philippnagel.com/feeds</title>
    <updated>2021-06-06T00:27:14.022Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new proposal on corporate tax synchronization]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81229</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/QsXPnO6qSek/the-new-proposal-on-corporate-tax-synchronization.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T19:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The G-7 nations have coordinated (NYT, FT here) to announce a minimum corporate tax rate of 15%.  Even if seen through, that doesn’t mean all rates must be at 15% or higher, rather if a rate is at 5% another country (the home base country?  the countries where the customers are?) gets to tack on […]
The post The new proposal on corporate tax synchronization appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81221</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/OnK8kRTwpAw/saturday-assorted-links-312.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T15:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Jim Jarmusch interview.  And Anthony Braxton interview. 2. Is the sperm-count crisis for real? (NYT) 3. Helsinki Complaints Choir.  And Tokyo. 4. There is no great stagnation. 5. Simone Biles in extreme slow motion.
The post Saturday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[*The Economist* on digital money]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81226</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/XK8V7GoKScg/the-economist-on-digital-money.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T05:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This multi-article section from a few weeks ago was very good.  Here is one excerpt: “It feels very significant that the countries which, apart from China, are most advanced, most active and most interested in cbdcs are the medium-sized emerging economies,” says Mr Landau. “They are too big to accept the loss of monetary autonomy, and […]
The post *The Economist* on digital money appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The regulatory cicada culture that is American]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81225</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/vQKFlw6H520/the-regulatory-cicada-culture-that-is-american.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T04:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As millions of cicadas began emerging in Loudoun County about two weeks ago, Chef Tobias Padovano at Cocina on Market in Leesburg began foraging for the noisy insects and serving them in tacos. That is, until last week when a customer ordered and ate the cicada tacos, only to later complain to the Loudoun County […]
The post The regulatory cicada culture that is American appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workers aren’t coming back]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81223</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/UbusmkYwxmY/workers-arent-coming-back.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T21:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data released by the Labor Department this morning show that last month, 61.6 percent of the working-age population were active in the labor force, either working in jobs or looking for them. That is essentially unchanged from the summer of 2020. The second most significant statistic is that wages are soaring. In May, average wages […]
The post Workers aren’t coming back appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whose big business? (Europe fact of the day)]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81222</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/fGebS4WqW9w/whose-big-business-europe-fact-of-the-day.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T15:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2000 nearly a third of the combined value of the world’s 1,000 biggest listed firms was in Europe, and a quarter of their profits. In just 20 years those figures have fallen by almost half. Europe is a place for companies such as Amazon and TikTok to find customers, not a base for local […]
The post Whose big business? (Europe fact of the day) appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friday assorted conspiracy links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81217</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/GqRaoUgfYRU/friday-assorted-conspiracy-links.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T11:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Vanity Fair on lab leak, with autistic hero. 2. NYT previews the UFO report (based on leaks, presumably).  USG is still puzzled, reports it is not “their stuff,” so I guess your “p” on alien origin should go up modestly.  Here is how the NYT web headline evolved.  The paper edition has the most […]
The post Friday assorted conspiracy links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does church keep you away from alcohol?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81219</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/VRYTFqLbw2M/does-church-keep-you-away-from-alcohol.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T07:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on a panel between 1980 and 2016, I find that one more Sunday with precipitation at the time of church increases yearly drug-related, alcohol-related and white-collar crimes. I do not find an effect for violent or property crimes. These effects are driven by more religious counties. Previous evidence showing negative effects of church attendance […]
The post Does church keep you away from alcohol? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto talks by Balaji and Vitalik]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81218</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/B-2VAoXpMUw/crypto-talks-by-balaji-and-vitalik.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T04:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a conference co-sponsored by Mercatus and Coin Center, here is Vitalik: Here is Balaji: Here are the other talks, by Nic Carter, Nevin Freeman, Erik Voorhees, and Peter van Valkenburgh.
The post Crypto talks by Balaji and Vitalik appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masking norms and Wokeism]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81216</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/OPOoAk50Gdw/masking-norms-and-wokeism.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T19:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is the close of my latest Bloomberg column: On a related note: Have you noticed that private universities often have a stronger “woke” culture, and less free speech, than public universities? This fact is also somewhat of an embarrassment for many libertarians. Though libertarian-leaning, I am myself happy to be teaching at a public […]
The post Masking norms and Wokeism appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Anderson of TED interviews me]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81214</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/PjCQhEdSTPo/chris-anderson-of-ted-interviews-me.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 50 years of little growth, new breakthroughs in science and medicine could mean the start of a whole new era of innovation! Economist @tylercowen paints a new picture of the future — and a road map to get us there. Listen on @applepodcasts: https://t.co/jNccIENQBo pic.twitter.com/Q8nQuEWRsX — TED Talks (@TEDTalks) June 3, 2021 Here is […]
The post Chris Anderson of TED interviews me appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thursday assorted links]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81207</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/5O8Lrz7yHKc/thursday-assorted-links-309.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T16:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. A visual of debt to gdp ratios.  Note the information is not strictly comparable across countries.  And where chess pieces go to die. 2. Profile of James Daunt (FT). 3. Research jobs at Charter Cities Institute. 4. United to buy 15 Boom supersonic aircraft. 5. These birds can see through magic tricks (NYT).
The post Thursday assorted links appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Update on Rapid Tests for COVID]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81199</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/14NhCAeH1y8/update-on-rapid-testing-for-covid.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year ago, I wrote Frequent, Fast, and Cheap is Better than Sensitive, arguing for rapid antigen tests: A number of firms have developed cheap, paper-strip tests for coronavirus that report results at-home in about 15 minutes but they have yet to be approved for use by the FDA because the FDA appears to […]
The post Update on Rapid Tests for COVID appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tabarrok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh fact of the day]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81213</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/qr1scf17K9M/bangladesh-fact-of-the-day-3.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T05:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month, Bangladesh’s Cabinet Secretary told reporters that GDP per capita had grown by 9% over the past year, rising to $2,227. Pakistan’s per capita income, meanwhile, is $1,543. In 1971, Pakistan was 70% richer than Bangladesh; today, Bangladesh is 45% richer than Pakistan. One Pakistani economist glumly pointed out that “it is in the realm of […]
The post Bangladesh fact of the day appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you call this a new service sector job?]]></title>
        <id>https://marginalrevolution.com/?p=81208</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/marginalrevolution/feed/~3/QgdexV3esIo/can-you-call-this-a-new-service-sector-job.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T04:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Taube has won a computer, a whitewater rafting trip, and several grills. There’s also the kayak, the powder-blue Coors Light onesie, and the Bruce Springsteen tickets. He recently took home $10,000 from Cost Plus World Market in its “World of Joy” sweepstakes. Recently, he found himself in the running for a trip to Antarctica, which would […]
The post Can you call this a new service sector job? appeared first on Marginal REVOLUTION.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tyler Cowen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.10.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.10.2"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T04:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: testing and CI/CD workflows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May Eris of the Month 2021: Eris Ἐρις by Matthias Jiury]]></title>
        <id>http://historiadiscordia.com/?p=9672</id>
        <link href="http://historiadiscordia.com/may-eris-of-the-month-2021-eris-%e1%bc%90%cf%81%ce%b9%cf%82-by-matthias-jiury/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T02:29:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Found on flickr. Send us your Eris of the Month Club submissions (more info here) by using the form at the bottom of The MGT. page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>themgt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booby Trapping the Ethereum Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>60a80b1a2c41740001d6fc2f</id>
        <link href="https://samczsun.com/booby-trapping-the-ethereum-blockchain/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T22:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is how an attacker could have hid a ticking time bomb on the Ethereum blockchain that, when triggered, would hard fork the entire network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samczsun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.9.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.9.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T06:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: experimental support for iTunes podcast feed: Demo | Source. With this new release, you can render an audio control to play the mp3 file and display iTunes episode duration. It is "experimental" due to these caveats:

This feature is currently only available through custom template.
iTunes has no strict format requirement for duration. The unit is most likely seconds but can be "hh:mm:ss" or "mm:ss" for some sources. A future version may expose a human readable string to the template.
No image support yet. Some shows might have disabled CORS or use a relative URL for image, which forces osmosfeed to download the image during build. A future version may support it.
You can't republish the podcast in the feed output. Supporting this goes beyond the scope of the project at the moment.
Fixed: the articles in template data were not sorted.
Thank you @Zenigata]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: UnhandledPromiseRejectionWarning: Error: At least one option must be a string]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.8.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.8.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T05:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changed: Smart summary truncation. When there is no dedicated summary (only Atom feed has it, and many sites don't use it) from the source, we check if the content/description (Both Atom and RSS) field is long enough to be full text. If so, it will be truncated into a "pseudo" summary. If not, we assume the source used the content field as summary, and it will be displayed in full length.
Thank you: @LooperXX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⚠ Deprecated: To accommodate the monorepo setup, the node version in all templates/demos/examples has changed from 14 to 16. This is not a breaking change as our compile target is still node 14, and node 16 is backward compatible. We still recommend you start using node-version: "16" in your .github/workflows/update-feed.yaml today to get the performance/security improvements from the newer node. See example
Chore: Reorganize to monorepo with npm workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T02:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: static files were unnecessarily copied for custom templates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.7.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.7.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T01:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: templating system. Demo | Source | Docs
Chore: rendering logic refactoring. Adopting functional paradigm.
Thank you @tianheg, @onnyyonn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.4.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Basic theme customization: Demo | Source | Docs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.6.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.6.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-10T08:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Link from the title of a subscription to its website.
Added: Store feedUrl and siteUrl for each source in cache.
Added: Semantic element (<time>) for timestamp on the UI.
Added: Semantic API for theming the default template. Demo | Source | Docs
Changed: Moved feed metadata from article level to feed level in cache.
Fixed: Any html-like text was stripped from title. Fixed with encoded text.
Removed: href for each source in cache. The value was never used so it's not a breaking change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.5.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.5.0"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T05:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Added: Atom feed generator
Added: Customizable site title
Added: Copy all files from static directory to the root of the site.
Changed: Favicon, css, and js assets now existing at site root level.
Chore: Excluded testing files from repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>